Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Recreation Committee: Minutes, etc., 1957-1964 (Box 5)
  - Recreation Committee: Misc. Materials (inc. Joe College), 1958-1963 (Box 5)
  - Admissions Office - "Student Contacts Committee", 1958-1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: Publicity, 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Building Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Lectures and Programs Records, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Board of Chairmen, 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Crosscurrents in Contemporary Life - A Commentary by Women" and "Contemporary Literature: A Post-Human Age?", March 1963, November 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Speakers, Ralph Ellison, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Proposed Speakers, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Speakers, Dr. Thomas Driver, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Speakers, Jules Feiffer, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Speakers, W.D. Snodgrass, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Speakers, Walt Kelly, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Applications for Committee, RESTRICTED, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Committee: "Contemporary Literature - A Post-Human Age," Miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 5)
  - Symposium Transcripts, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: George C. McGhee, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: James F. Byrnes, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Glen Seaborg, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: J. Edgar Hoover, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Ambassador Sergio Rojas, 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: N.B.C. Forum, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Harold Taylor, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibitors, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - CORE [Congress of Racial Equality], 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Columbia Law Students Visit, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Carolina Delivery Service, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Campus Tours, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Duke Tour, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - European Travel Group Flight, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Newcomers Club, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Board of Governors Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Board of Governors Minutes and Agendas, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Special Services Committee Last Lecture Series: Dr. T. Ropp; Refusals by Dr, Woodhall (med) and Dean Cleland, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Special Services Committee Distinguished Visitors: Gandar, Manning, Schweitzer, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Special Services Committee Distinguished Guests Program; 1964 correspondence between Lynda Whitley and Ella Pratt, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Special Services Committee General, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Building Commission, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Lectures and Programs Records, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Brochures/Miscellaneous Records, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Board of Governors Records, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Union Yearly Report, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - National Screen Service Corporation Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964-1965 Aircade Visit, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Bassett Lecture Series - "The Young Lovers", 1964 (Box 5)
  - Box Office Reports, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Reynolds Price, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator Barry Goldwater (Clippings), 1964 (Box 5)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Davidson Nicol, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 1964 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Seminar Feb. 21-23 1965, General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Amiya Chakravarty, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dr. Juscelino Kubitschnek, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibition; Brochures, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibitions, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Publicity Committee, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Visual Arts Committee: Performing Arts, circa 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Joe College Committee: Joe College Weekend Miscellaneous, 1954-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: UN Model Assembly Speaker, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Malcolm Cowley, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Cinus Pauling, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator Wayne Morse, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Bishop James Pike, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Theodore Sorensen, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Richard Gilman, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Chris Kraft, 1966-1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adventure Series, "The High Road to Skiing" - Hans Gmoser, November 14, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adventure Series, "Red China" - Jens Bjere, October 3, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adam Clayton Powell, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Brochure File, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: N. Hanks, J. Ordway, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adventure Series, John Mayer, "New Face of India", February 13, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adventure Series, Geza de Rosner, March 7, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General Responses, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Miscellaneous (inc. correspondence to Martin Luther King, Jr. after his Nobel Peace Prize selection, 1964-1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Committee Evaluation - Major Speakers, undated, circa 1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Major Speakers Brochure, 1956-1968 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Mr. Walter Reuther, 1957-1959 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Henry Cabot Lodge, 1956-1961 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Henry Ford II, 1956-1961 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Werner Von Braun, 1959-1961 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Arthur Miller, 1959-1961 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1960-1962 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Agency Speakers, 1955-1962 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Contacts/General, 1959-1962 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Robert Frost, 1959-1962 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1959-1963 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Nelson Rockefeller, 1960-1964 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Publicity - Symposium on the South, 1963-1965 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Abba Eban, 1957-1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Mr. Howard K. Smith, 1957-1964 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: German Ambassador, 1961-1963 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Pauline Frederick, 1961-1963 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Erich Fromm, 1961-1963 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Vladimir Dedijer, 1963-1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Seminar Brochure, 1963-1966 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Justice Byron R. White, 1964-1967 (Box 6)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: "The Computer and the Mind of Man," Financial Statement, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: "The Computer and the Mind of Man," Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: "The Computer and the Mind of Man," Contacted Speakers, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Undergraduate Life at Duke" and "The Individual in Mass Society, April and November, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: Minutes, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Symposium Committee: Symposium 1964 Publicity Materials, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Joe College, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Administrative and Governing Records (Griffith Files), 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Newsletters, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Recreation Committee: Captain Johnson, USNR, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Recreation Committee: Raphael Green, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Special Events Committee: Last Lectures, Drs. Pail Hardin and W.W. Kulski, 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Special Events Committee: Last Lectures, Dr. Anne Scott, April 13, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Box Office Records, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Senator George McGovern, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dean Jacques Barzun, 1956-1965 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Dean Burch, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Martin Agronsky, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: Adventure Series (4 folders), 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Educational Affairs Committee: General, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Student Union General: Major Fields and Receptions, Seminars, Student-Faculty, Foreign Students, Last Lectures, 1963-1965 (Box 7)
  - Student Union Ticket Records (bulk 1965), 1961-1965 (Box 7)
  - "New Union": Change from "Student Union" to "University Union", 1965-1969 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: Miscellaneous, including minutes, 1964-1966 (Box 7)
  - People to People Program, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Experiment in International Living (2 folders), 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - United Nations, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Joe College Committee: Joe College Weekends, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Donald L. Velde Enterprises Correspondence, 1958-1965 (Box 7)
  - Newsletters, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - European Travel Group Flight, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "The Impact of Education, Science, and Technology on the South" and "A Question of Values", April and November, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Research in Progress - Science in the Making" (part of NC Junior Science & Humanities Symposium), March 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Participants, Russell Kirk, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Participants, Dr. Harvey Cox; Hugh Hefner correspondence, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Participants, Lawrence Lipton, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Participants, Harriet Pilpel, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: "A Question of Values," Finances, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Campus Services Committee: Distinguished Visitors, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Campus Services Committee: People to People, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Campus Services Committee: Civil Rights and Securities Seminars; Addis and Crofut, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Campus Services Committee: Addis and Crofut, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Campus Services Committee: General, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - House Counselors Meeting, October 6, 1965 (Box 7)
  - United Nations, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - European Travel Group Flight, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Speakers, 1962-1966 (Box 7)
  - Joe College, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Boares Head Banquet, April 25, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Outline for College Union and Duke Union, undated (Box 7)
  - Ticket Information, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Board of Governors Records, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Union Rolls/Personnel Records, 1958-1967 (Box 7)
  - Organization Heads, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Concepts of a University" Summer Symposium, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: Public Relations; Build-Ups. Joe Durre; Joe Harris, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: Transcript Requests, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: Participants, Dr. Knight, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Symposium Committee: Participants, Dr. Muscatine, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibitions, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1960s-1970s (Box 7)
  - Carolina Weekend Concert: Martha and The Vandellas, Marvin Gaye, Brenda Holloway, 1967 (Box 7)
  - University of California Davis Art Program, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Boares Head Banquet, April 20, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Box Office Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Records, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Quadrangle Pictures: Financial Records, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Special Services Committee: International Students, 1964-1966 (Box 8)
  - Campus Services Committee: Letters, Agendas, Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Campus Services Committee: Last Lecture Series, Dr. John Altrocchi, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Campus Services Committee: General, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Campus Services Committee: LSD Seminar Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - European Travel Group Flight, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Board of Governors Administrative Records, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Board of Governors Records, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Board of Chairmen Records, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - B.O.G. Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Brochures, 1964-1968 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: Minutes and Correspondence, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Spoonful (Major Attractions Event), 1967 (Box 8)
  - "The Lovin' Spoonful", 1967 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: Panel - Dr. Friedenberg, Manuscript, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Impact: The Postwar Generation", 1967 (Box 8)
  - Carolina Weekend Dance: Showmen & The Fabulous Five, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Quadrangle Pictures Schedules, 1965-1968 (Box 8)
  - Semester Calendar Requests, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Shows, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - Visual Arts Committee: Film Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - B.O.G. -- Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - B.O.G. -- Resolution, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Educative Involvement Committee (3 folders), 1968 (Box 8)
  - Educative Involvement Committee [Letter to Co-curricular Chairman], 1968 (Box 8)
  - Performing Arts: Young Artist Concert, Yoko Nozaki, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Board of Governors Records, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Board of Chairmen Governing and Administrative Records, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Building/Facilities Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - European Travel Group Flight, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Symposium Committee: "Kapow; The Electric Media", 1968 (Box 8)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: London Grafica, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibits, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - ASDU Relations, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Union Calendar, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Student Union Paid Invoices, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Student Union (General), 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Controversial Speakers, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Union Planning Committee, 1968 (Box 8)
  - N.E.C. (National Entertainment Conference), 1968 (Box 8)
  - Financial Report, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Academic Reform [includes Student Proposal for Mutual Cooperation through a Student-Trustee Committee], 1968 (Box 8)
  - Annual Counselors Luncheon (in Old Trinity Room), October 1, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Policy, 1968-1973 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
  - Event Calendars, 1960s (Box 8)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Art Exhibition Sources, 1967-1970 (Box 8)
  - Summer Session, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Sources, 1969-1976 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects, including Adam Clayton Powell visit, 1967-1970 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Symposium, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Union Governance References, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Cinematic Arts: Box Office Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Proposed Policy Manual, 1970 (Box 8)
  - U.S. State Dept, undated, circa 1960s (Box 9)
  - ACU-I Region I Conference (staff-leadership in the Union Committees), 1967 (Box 9)
  - 1966 Symposium Transcript, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts, circa 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium committee roster, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Potential Speakers Contacted, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Arrangements for Gordon Grant and Nancy Cardwell, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Off-Campus and Alumni Relations, Bob Waldman, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Secretary's File (minutes), 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Faculty Relations - Conrad Smith, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence - Speakers, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Completed Arrangements, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Dr. E.G. Williamson, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Outside Finances - Karl Clauset, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Finances - Treasurer's File, Dave Henderson, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Publicity - Dale Norton, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence Completed, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Committee Work - Assignments and Reports, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Misc. Correspondence, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: "Concepts of a University", 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Notes and Minutes, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Sundry Clippings and Records, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: David Harris, 1966 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Pre-Artists Series Seminars, 1966-1968 (Box 9)
  - Photos/News Clippings [3 folders], circa 1960s (Box 9)
  - Joe College Committee: Box Supper, April 26, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence and Minutes, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Seminars, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: General Records, 1967 (Box 9)
  - 1964-1968 Symposium Committee Financial Records, 1964-1968 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Pre-Symposium Build-Up, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Participants - Jack Newfield, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Participants - Seymour Lipset, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Participants - Seymour Halleck, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Edgar Z. Friedenberg, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Finances, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Off Campus Relations - Phil Snead, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Co-Curricular Activities - Jeff Davis and Gen Christy, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Joe College, 1967 (Box 9)
  - Visual Arts Committee: Film Series, Spring 1968 (Box 9)
  - Yearly Report - Ella Fountain Pratt, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Symposium: Treasurer's File, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Joe College Weekend: Float Building and Dance, April 15, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Joe College Weekend: Lawn Concert, April 26, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Joe College Weekend: Warwick-Lewis Concert, April 17, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Joe College Weekend, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Galleries, circa 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts: Drama Committee, circa 1968-1975 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Carlos Montoya, January 4, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Drama Committee - The Fantasticks, February 9, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Preservation Hall Jazz, February 15, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: NC School of Arts - "Nutcracker", 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: "Curlew River", October 25, 1968 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: North Carolina Symphony, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Gordon Lightfoot, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Nikolais Dance Company, April 28-30, 1969 (Box 9)
  - Regional Programming: Carolina Union, undated (Box 9)
  - Student Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Board of Governors Records, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Board of Governors: Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Reorganization Records, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous Records (clippings, etc.), 1970s (Box 10)
  - Brochures, Handouts, Pamphlets, 1960s-1970s (Box 10)
  - Expenditure Authorizations, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Educative Involvement Committee: Distinguished Professors Seminars, Freshman Week, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Educative Involvement Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Travel (European Flights), 1969 (Box 10)
  - United Nations, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Advertising Information, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Spring Mills Show, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Mrs. Sheila Pratt, March 6-20, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: London Grafica, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Poetry Poster Exhibit, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Mrs. Dorothy Westby Moeller, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Mr. Jeremy North, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: American Federation of Art, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Roten Galleries, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: NYC Scene, Dr. Bruce Schlein, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Security, Insurance Policy, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: "Metropolitan Scene", 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Southern Highland Handicraft Guild, 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - Graphic Arts Committee: Tapestry - Sylvia Heyden, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Programming Council: Minutes [includes Union Board and Executive Council Minutes], 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Programming Council: Budget Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Rena Kazmann, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - History: First UUB Exec. Meetings, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Joe College Committee: Joe College Weekends, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Public Relations (Association of African Students), 1969, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Box Office Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Philidor Trio, October 5, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Lucas Hoving Dance Company, October 15-17, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: "The Play of Herod", November 24, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: "The Nutcracker Ballet", December 16-17, 1969 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: NC Symphony Orchestra, March 10, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Scruggs, Doc Watson, April 11, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Tom Rush - Folk Festival, April 12, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Southern Cultural Folk Festival, April 18, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Folk Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Performing Arts Committee: Mimi Garrard Dance Theatre, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Committee: Meeting Space - Classrooms, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Facilities Committee: General Records, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
  - Recreation Committee: Coffeehouse, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Recreation Committee: Games Room Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Recreation Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Programming Committee: The Happening, September 18-20, 1970 (Box 10)
  - "Mylon" Bill, January-February, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Living Groups Proposal, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Misc. Records, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Building/Facilities Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Calendar Quotations, 1968-1970 (Box 10)
  - Public Relations (shirts), 1970 (Box 10)
  - ASDU Relevant Legislation, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Student Organizations, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Jewish Affairs Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - WDBS Contract w/Union, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Board Handouts, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Major Attractions: Board Administrative Materials, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Brief for Mr. Griffith, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Performance Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Advertising Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Living Group Mailing Addresses, 1970-1971 (Box 10)